Arthur Espartinez

Legaspi, Bicol Region, Philippines



artespar85@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/arthur-espartinez-a2b1ba218

Summary

I am Arthur Espartinez, 25 years old, a full stack developer from the Philippines. I am a registered Mechanical Engineer but decided for a career shift because coding has always been one of my passion. That's why I decided to take an intensive coding bootcamp to further hone my skills.

I would like to contribute to your organization as a full-stack developer, leveraging my ability to develop E-commerce web applications using readily available-web applications. With my passion for learning, I will be able to take part in empowering your team with my newly found coding experience.

Experience

Student

Zuitt - Coding Bootcamp Philippines

Aug 2021 - Sep 2021 (2 months)

Capstone Project 1 - Static Website

- Created a static personal portfolio website
- Used HTML, CSS and Javacscript
- Hosted using Github

Student

Zuitt - Coding Bootcamp Philippines

Aug 2021 - Sep 2021 (2 months)

Capstone Project 2 - E-commerce API Development

- Created an API development of an e-commerce using Express.js, Node.js and MongoDB with the following functionalities:
- a. User registration and authentication
- b. Admin authorization
- c. Creating of orders
- Hosted using Heroku

Student

Zuitt - Coding Bootcamp Philippines

Aug 2021 - Sep 2021 (2 months)

Capstone Project 3 - Full-Stack Website

- Created e-commerce website using MERN Stack (MongoDB, Express.js, React.js, Node.js)
- Created the frontend application using React.JS
- Created the backend server using Express.JS, Node.JS and MongoDB as database
- Hosted using Vercel and Heroku



LAMVER CONSOLIDATED COMPLEX DEVELOPMENT CORPORATION

Jun 2019 - Feb 2020 (9 months)

■ Service Advisor

Inframachineries Corporation

Nov 2017 - Jan 2019 (1 year 3 months)

After-sales service and maintenance engineer on heavy equipment like excavator and loader

Education

Zuitt - Coding Bootcamp Philippines

Postgraduate/ Certificate Course, Web Development

Aug 2021 - Sep 2021

Attended an 8-week full time web development training at Zuitt Coding Bootcamp in a live online format. I learned how to create static web apps, a backend application supporting its interactive web app, and an understanding of client and server interaction.

Bicol University

Bachelor's degree, Mechanical Engineering Jun 2013 - Apr 2017

Licenses & Certifications

Mechanical Engineer - Bicol University

Issued Nov 2017 - Expires Jan 2023

Skills

Front-end Development • Back-End Web Development • Full-Stack Development • Lead Generation • Search Engine Optimization (SEO) • Web Development • Adobe Photoshop • WordPress • Microsoft Office • Microsoft Excel